{
    "subject": "resource/Flash_of_Genius_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/director",
    "object": "resource/Marc_Abraham",
    "human_readable": "The director of the film Flash of Genius is Marc Abraham.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9880886673927307,
            "question": "Is Marc Abraham the director of Flash of Genius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8935191631317139,
            "question": "Marc Abraham directed which film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8855620622634888,
            "question": "Who directed the film Flash of Genius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8853631019592285,
            "question": "What film was directed by Marc Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8537996411323547,
            "question": "Who is the director behind the film Flash of Genius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8097800016403198,
            "question": "Who is responsible for directing the movie Flash of Genius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7665979266166687,
            "question": "What is the name of the director who made Flash of Genius?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7261005640029907,
            "question": "Can you name a film directed by Marc Abraham?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5945348739624023,
            "question": "What movie did Marc Abraham direct?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5923206210136414,
            "question": "Which film was a project by Marc Abraham?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The director of the film Flash of Genius is Marc Abraham.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3888_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What movie did Marc Abraham direct?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3888_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a film directed by Marc Abraham?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3888_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the director who made Flash of Genius?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3888_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3888_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe query states that \"The director of the film Flash of Genius is Marc Abraham,\" which is supported by multiple documents, including those for files 16.txt, 17.txt, and 56.txt."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}